duration: 30 # seconds
enabled: true
messages:
  start: "<green>Solve <white>%question%</white><green> to win a prize!"
  end:
    won: "<green><bold>!</bold> <white>%player_name%</white> has won the round in <yellow>%time%<yellow> <white>seconds</white>!"
    timed-out: "<green><bold>!</bold> No one won that round, the answer was <yellow>%answers%"

questions:
  - question: "What is the name of the block used to craft torches?"
    answers:
      - "stick"
      - "coal"
  - question: "What is the name of the hostile mob that explodes?"
    answers:
      - "creeper"
  - question: "What is the name of the game mode where players have infinite resources?"
    answers:
      - "creative mode"
  - question: "What is the name of the tool used to break dirt and stone blocks?"
    answers:
      - "pickaxe"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that players spawn on when they first join a world?"
    answers:
      - "grass block"
  - question: "What is the name of the red, fiery dimension that can be accessed through a Nether portal?"
    answers:
      - "Nether"
  - question: "What is the name of the flying creature that drops leather when killed?"
    answers:
      - "bat"
  - question: "What is the name of the neutral mob that can be tamed with bones?"
    answers:
      - "wolf"
  - question: "What is the name of the material used to create armor?"
    answers:
      - "iron"
      - "diamond"
      - "gold"
  - question: "What is the name of the food that restores the most hunger points?"
    answers:
      - "golden carrot"
      - "cooked porkchop"
      - "steak"
  - question: "What is the name of the rare ore that can be found underground?"
    answers:
      - "diamond"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that is used to create a bed?"
    answers:
      - "wool"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that grows wheat?"
    answers:
      - "farmland"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to make a furnace?"
    answers:
      - "cobblestone"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to craft arrows?"
    answers:
      - "flint"
      - "stick"
      - "feather"
  - question: "What is the name of the material used to create tools and weapons?"
    answers:
      - "iron"
      - "diamond"
      - "gold"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to create a ladder?"
    answers:
      - "sticks"
  - question: "What is the name of the passive mob that can be milked?"
    answers:
      - "cow"
  - question: "What is the name of the item used to craft a fishing rod?"
    answers:
      - "string"
  - question: "What is the name of the item used to craft a bow?"
    answers:
      - "sticks"
      - "string"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to create a door?"
    answers:
      - "wood planks"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to create a boat?"
    answers:
      - "wood planks"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to create a chest?"
    answers:
      - "chest"
  - question: "What is the name of the block that can be used to create a crafting table?"
    answers:
      - "wood planks"